Lynn Hershman-Leeson Papers M1452
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Audio-Visual Materials, 1
  - Subseries 1.52: Unidentified Film, 1.52
    - San Francisco Art Institute "Father Guido Sarducci plug"; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 5 min. (Carton 38, Folder 16)
    - [Anne Gerber Footage]; undated (2 items), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 38, Folder 17)
    - Lynn in Europe Dub from HI8; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Original; 20 min. (Carton 39, Folder 12)
    - Lynn in Warsaw; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 39, Folder 13)
    - [illegible] panel; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 39, Folder 14)
    - Inter Arts Presentation; Laurie Anderson; 1987 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 00:10:30:00 (Carton 39, Folder 15)
    - Charles [illegible] CBS; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element] (Carton 39, Folder 16)
    - Project Documentation; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 39, Folder 17)
    - Heo; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 39, Folder 18)
    - Sex Tape; 1987-01-12 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 42, Folder 1)
    - Clip, Klapp, Bum; 1987-11-06 (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 42, Folder 2)
    - Graveyard & Funeral Footage; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 42, Folder 3)
    - [various clips]; undated (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub (Carton 42, Folder 4)
    - Flight Simulators, Tank Simulators, War Games; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 42, Folder 5)
    - [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 60 min. (Carton 42, Folder 6)
    - Graveyards Funeral Home; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 42, Folder 7)
    - MTV; 1992-07-22 (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 42, Folder 8)
    - judith bethleheim; 1989-03-16 (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 120 min. (Carton 42, Folder 9)
    - George's Motorcycle Footage, Bar Scene; 1990-12-18 (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 42, Folder 10)
    - [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Master; 75 min. (Carton 42, Folder 11)
    - [various footage]; undated (9 items), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 42, Folder 12)
    - A; undated, [unidentified director/producer] (1 item), Film: 8mm Full Coat Magnetic; [unidentified element] (Carton 44, Folder 1)
    - Jane Caputi; undated (1 item), Audio: Cassette; [unidentified element] (Carton 44, Folder 2)
    - Todd Gitlin; 1992-03-29 (1 item), Audio: Cassette; [unidentified element]; 90 min. (Carton 44, Folder 3)
    - Juron Part II; undated (1 item), Audio: Cassette; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 44, Folder 4)
    - [audio sources]; undated (20 items), Audio: Cassette; Dub (Carton 44, Folder 5)
    - [audio sources]; undated (4 items), Audio: Cassette; Commercial (Carton 44, Folder 6)
    - Giselle - Act I + II; undated (1 item), Audio: DAT; [unidentified element]; 90 min. (Carton 44, Folder 7)
    - Soundtrack Music; undated (1 item), Audio: DAT; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 44, Folder 8)
    - Bars and Tone; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 10 min. (Carton 44, Folder 9)
    - Sea Cut [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 44, Folder 10)
    - Commercials [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub (Carton 44, Folder 11)
    - Merle BeC; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 44, Folder 12)
    - [illegible] CD Rom; 1994-11-05 (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 5 min. (Carton 44, Folder 13)
    - Bumps, Invision, Work Tape; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 44, Folder 14)
    - New Change Seattle; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 60 min. (Carton 44, Folder 15)
    - [unidentified]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 44, Folder 16)
    - Tom Coull Sense 8; 1992-03-29 (2 items), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 44, Folder 17)
    - Scott Foster/others; 1992-03-29 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 44, Folder 18)
    - Scott Fisher; 1992-03-29 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 44, Folder 19)
    - Jane Caputi; 1992-11-11 (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 44, Folder 20)
    - Todd Gitlin; 1992-03-29 (2 items), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 44, Folder 21)
    - Jaron Part 1-2; 1992-12 (2 items), Video: U-matic; [unidentified element]; 30 min. (Carton 44, Folder 22)
    - Pete's Harry BBQ Story -Ed, Movement/Gesture Story; undated (1 item), Video: VHS-C; [unidentified element]; 20 min. (Carton 44, Folder 23)
    - YR Sound w/TC, Media Band Casting Selects; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 50, Folder 1)
    - Keen Music Back Up; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 60 min. (Carton 50, Folder 2)
    - Alive camera source, bruce demo, bj demo, naration; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Original; 30 min. (Carton 50, Folder 3)
    - Master [illegible] Mirror installation; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Master; 30 min. (Carton 50, Folder 4)
    - Raw Sirius Source, Bruce Demo, Galiko source, Marc NTSC source slides; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 50, Folder 5)
    - Dub from edit box; undated (1 item), Video: Digital Betacam; Dub; 12 min. (Carton 50, Folder 6)
    - Pearl; undated (1 item), Video: Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 50, Folder 7)
    - Cambodia Free Speech; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 20 min. (Carton 50, Folder 8)
    - Bomb Sources; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 10 min. (Carton 50, Folder 9)
    - [illegible]; undated (1 item), Video: U-matic; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 50, Folder 10)
    - Four Dogs Married Together; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: Betacam SP; [unidentified element]; 5 min. (Carton 50, Folder 11)
    - 200A; undated (1 item): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: 1" open reel; [unidentified element]; 2.5 in. (Carton 69, Folder 5)
    - Up Dub #100-300; undated (3 items): Lynn Hershman director/producer, Video: 1" open reel; Dub (Carton 70, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 1.53: Films by Others, 1.53
    - A Visit to China's Mao Country; undated, Ellie Coppola (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 00:36:24:00 (Carton 23, Folder 4)
    - 9 Seconds Later; 1997, LG Williams (1 item), Video: VHS; Dub; 00:01:00:00 (Carton 23, Folder 5)
- Series 2: Film Projects: Correspondence and Materials, 2
  - Subseries 1.01: America's Finest, 1.01
    - America's Finest 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Conceptual and Technical Research 1993 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Grant's Application 1993 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Contracts 1993 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Targa and Information 1993 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Software 1993 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Software and Installation 1993 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Illustrated Storyboard 1993 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Photographs 1993 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Exhibitions - Interactive Media Festival 1993 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Exhibitions - Mill Valley Film Festival 1993 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Exhibitions - The Digital Village 1993 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Exhibitions - Rijksmuseum Twenthe/"Obsessions" 1993 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Exhibitions - Lab Five, Center for Contemporary Art 1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Exhibitions - Video Positive, International Festival of Electronic Arts 1993 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Exhibitions - 235 Media, Cologne Art Faire 1993 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Exhibitions - Miscellaneous Exhibits 1993 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence 1993 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 2.02: Chain Reaction, 2.02
    - Chain Reaction 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Chain Reaction - T-Shirt 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Brochures 1983 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Scripts/Lyrics 1983 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Proposals for Project 1983 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Notes/plans/etc. 1983 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1983 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Contracts 1983 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Invoices 1983 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Editorial Log 1983 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 2.03: Chimaera Monographie: Lynn Hershman 1992, 2.03
    - Chimaera Monographie: Lynn Hershman 1992 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - "Chimaera Monographie" 1992 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Textual Drafts (1 of 2) 1992 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Textual Drafts (2 of 2) 1992 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Notes 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Bibliography and Exhibition History 1992 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Moira Roth Interview and Essay 1992 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence 1992 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Chimaera Images with Text 1992 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Preliminary Proof 1992 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 2.04: Conceiving Ada, 2.04
    - "Tilda Moments" Hilton Als 1997 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - "Lust..." Courtney Weaver 1997 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - "That's Snow Business" Ariel Foxman 1997 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - "Concevoir Tilda" Jerry Stafford 1997 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - "The Buzz" Stephen Galloway 1997 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - "Tilda Swinton Decides It's Time for Acting" The New York Times August 5, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - "An Actress Decides It's Time for Acting" The New Yorl Times August 5, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - "Swinton's portrayal aids 'Tecknolust;" San Francisco Chronicle September 7, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - PR 1997 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - PR 1997 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Finances 1997 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Sound 1997 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Budget 1997 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Scene Breakdown 1997 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Draft 26 1997 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence 1996 1997 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Claudia 1997 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Claudia Tronnier ZDF 1997 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Rosetta 1997 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco State University 1997 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Portrero Nuevo Fund & Fundraising 1997 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Court: Lynn Hershman V. Board of Regents of San Francisco State University 1997 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence & Art Collection Pamphlets 1997 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Conceiving Ada Draft 26- June 1997 1997 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Ada Legal paperwork 1997 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Ada Contracts 1997 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Potential Crew Resumes 1997 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Interns 1997 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Invoices, Receipts 1997 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Hotels 1997 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Travel 1997 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Crew 1997 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Crew 1997 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Budget 1997 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Misc Correspondence 1997 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Misc Notes & Papers 1997 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Virtual Set Patent 1997 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Blank Contract Forms 1997 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - AAton des Artistes 1997 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Film Stock & Processes 1997 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - IFFCON 1997 1997 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Cinematographer Notes 1997 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Casting Agents 1997 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Cast List 1997 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Casting Correspondence 1997 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Non-Disclosure & Confidentiality Consent Forms 1997 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Actor Offers 1997 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - SAG Information 1997 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Screen Play Synopsis 1997 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Script Breakdown 1997 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Actors Search Pool 2 of 2 1997 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Actors Search Pool 1 of 2 1997 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Continuity Report 1997 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Day 6 1997 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Day 7 1997 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Day 13 July 29th 1997 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Day 14 July 30th 1997 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Day 15th July 31st 1997 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Day 16 August 1st 1997 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Day 17 August 2 1997 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Day 18 August 5th 1997 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Memos 1997 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Notes/Logs - final Assemble & Change Lists 1997 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Final Selects / Logs 1997 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Love Scene Lists 1997 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Pull Lists 1997 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Scene Pull Lists 1997 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - 1st Beta Assemble Lists 1997 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Assemble Lists 1997 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Optical Lists 1997 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - NG Lists 1997 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - NG Optical Lists 1997 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Final Optical Lists 1997 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Misc 3.5" Floppy Disks 1997 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Research Articles 1997 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Donations/Craft Services 1997 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Telephone Numbers & Contacts 1997 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - ADR 1997 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Digital Phenomena 1997 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - PostProduction Notes 1997 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Props 1997 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Graphics 1997 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Outpost 1997 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Monaco Labs 1997 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Call Sheets 1997 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Shooting Schedule 1997 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Camera Rentals 1997 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Location Imagery 1997 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Locations 1997 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - The Engine 1997 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - People Images 1997 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Babbage Lab 1997 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Country Life Copyright 1997 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - National Monuments 1997 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Image Research 1997 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - National Portrait Gallery 1997 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - National Science Museum 1997 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Blue Screen F.X. 1997 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Art Direction 1997 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Bird Story Board 1997 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Birds and Automatae 1997 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Costume Designer 1997 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Post Production Music 1997 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Lawrence Camplings Memos 1997 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Release Forms 1997 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Character Breakdown 1997 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Lynn's Notes 1997 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Ricardo Aronovich 1997 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - John Perry Barlow 1997 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Debbie Brubaker 1997 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Mette Stroemfeldt 1997 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Jesse Drew 1997 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Anna Wagner 1997 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Henry Rosenthal 1997 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Tilda Swinton 1997 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Lois Bianchi 1997 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Timothy Leary 1997 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - David L Brown 1997 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Claudia Tronnier 1997 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Cathrin Cartlidge 1997 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 2.05: Dante Hotel, 2.05
    - Dante Hotel 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Catalogue 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Artifacts: "Nail File" (photocopy) 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Media 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Writings 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook and Miscellaneous 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 2.06: Deep Contact, 2.06
    - Deep Contact 1989 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Technical/Conceptual Research 1989 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Technical/Conceptual Writings 1989 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Branching System 1989 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Script 1989 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Photographs 1989 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Disks 1989 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Music 1989 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Grants 1989 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Budget 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Advance Orders 1989 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Receipts 1989 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Correspondance 1989 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Exhibitions 1989 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - SF Moma 1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Fresno Art Museum 1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - US Press 1989 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Finnish Press 1989 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - German Press 1989 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Danish Press 1989 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Italian Press 1989 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Sara Roberts & Thesis 1989 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2.07: Difference Engine # 3, 2.07
    - Difference Engine 1995-1998 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Project Proposal (1 of 2) 1995-1998 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Project Proposal (2 of 2) 1995-1998 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Technical Development 1995-1998 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Schematics 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Museum Blueprints 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Catalogues 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Project Participants 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Equipment 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Finances 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Timeline 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Schedule 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Media 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Photography 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 2.08: Dream Weekend, 2.08
    - Dream Weekend: Australia: Angel Island bus trip photo; 2 performance postcards, September 15-17 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Dream Weekend: Australia: Photographs 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Dream Weekend: Australia: Public relations 1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Dream Weekend: Australia: Negatives, proofsheets 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Dream Weekend: Australia:project abstract 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dream Weekend: Australia: Research [1 of 2] 1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Dream Weekend: Australia: Research [2 of 2] 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Dream Weekend: Australia: Financial 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Dream Weekend: Australia: Correspondence 1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Dream Weekend: Australia: Development [1 of 2] 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Dream Weekend: Australia: Development [2 of 2] 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - [Untitled audiotape found in Australia Development folder] (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2.09: Elizabeth Frankenstein, 2.09
    - Claudia 1999[?] (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Frankenstein/Sent 1999[?] (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - The Gendered Atom 1999[?] (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Frankenstein Scripts 1999[?] (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Bound Frankenstein Script Draft 1 1999[?] (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Bound Frankenstein Script Draft 16 1999[?] (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Bound Frankenstein Script Draft 8 1999[?] (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Bound Frankenstein Script Draft 8 1999[?] (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Frankenstein Script 1999[?] (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Bills 1999[?] (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Frankenstein Script Draft 2 1999[?] (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Revisions & Comments 1999[?] (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Synopsis Frankenstein 1999[?] (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Frankenstein 1999[?] (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Actors Frankenstein 1999[?] (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Jeff Dowd Frankenstein 1999[?] (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - The Edelweiss Pirates 1999[?] (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - The Edelweiss Pirates 1999[?] (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Sundance Institute: Correspondences, Brochures, etc. 1999[?] (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Draft 7: The Memoirs of Elizabeth Frankenstein 1999[?] (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Sundance Misc.: Correspondences, brochures, etc. 1999[?] (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Draft 7: Frankenstein, Sundance Misc. 1999[?] (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Sundance Screenwriter's Lab 1/99 Frankenstein 1999[?] (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Frankenstein Budget 1999[?] (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Frankenstein Misc. correspondences and notes 1999[?] (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Sundance Institute Letter & Bio 1999[?] (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Bio 1999[?] (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Misc. Press: Hershman 1999[?] (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Frankenstein: misc. correspondence 1999[?] (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Ex-machina 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Theodore 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Scripts, correspondences 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Actors 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Legal Documents 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Job Listing 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Characters 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Tilda Swinton 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Production 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Robbie Muller 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Actors 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Jeff Dowd 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Background Information 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Casting 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Contacts 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - German Film Fund 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - The Gendered Atom 1999[?] (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Funding 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Images 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Misc 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Script 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Draft 10 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Scenes 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - PR 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Conceiving Ada Material 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Navigating the Next Millennium 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - ZDF 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Tax Correspondence 1999[?] (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - ZDF 1999[?] (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Claudia 1999[?] (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2.10: Endangered Species, 2.10
    - Endangered Species [1 of 2] 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Endangered Species [2 of 2] 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Endangered Species: Invitations, brochures 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Endangered Species: Press, reviews 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Women Surrealists: Carrington Project 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Endangered Species: Fire permit; releases 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Endangered Species: Publicity 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Endangered Species: Scripts 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Endangered Species: Spectrum Foundation, Eyes and Ears Foundation 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Endangered Species: Correspondence 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Endangered Species:Risk of Art proposal 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2.11: Fire Works, 2.11
    - Fire Works 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Writings 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Visual Research 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - One Story Building (1of2) - Exhibit 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - One Story Building (2of2) - Photographs 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Two Stories Building (1of5) - Exhibit 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Two Stories Building (2of5) - Budget 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Two Stories Building (3of5) - Writings 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Two Stories Building (4of5) - Correspondence 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Two Stories Building (5of5) - Photographs 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Fire Sale (1of2) Exhibit 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Fire Sale (2of2) Photographs 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 2.12: The Floating Museum 1974-1978, 2.12
    - Richard Kramier 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Elizabeth King 1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Robert Janz 1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Pearl Jones 1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Robbin Henderson 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Helen Dammenberg 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Joya Cary 1974 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - G. Chrisman 1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Judy Barry 1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Mary Bondarowig 1974 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Nancy Blanchard 1974 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Judith Binder 1974 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Judith Azur 1974 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Margo St. James 1974 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Douglass Davis 1974 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Theresa Hak Kyung Cha 1974 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - The Harrisons [1 of 2] 1974 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - The Harrisons [2 of 2] 1974 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Suzanne Lacy 1974 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Mike Osterhout 1974 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Problematic Photography 1974 (Box 26, Folder 21)